{
  "decks": [
    {
      "category": "Ruby",
      "flashcards": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "What do you call a method with exclamation point? 2 answers.",
          "answer": "Bang version of the method or unsafe method."
        },
      
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "What is difference between gsub and sub?",
          "answer": "gsub is 'general' sub and replaces all instances. sub only replaces first instance."
        },
      
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "How do you use nil?",
          "answer": "puts 'Couldn't find answer' if [1, 2, 3].index(42).nil?"
        },
      
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "Object that is a block of code that can be bound to a set of local variables",
          "answer": "Proc"
        },
      
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "Turn 'Tom', 'Bill', 'Jerry' into the string 'Tom, Bill, Jerry'",
          "answer": "Use array.join(', ')"
        },
      
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "What is a function declaration compared to a function expression?",
          "answer": "declaration: function myFunc(){ ... }, expression: var myFunc = function() { ... }"
        },
      
        {
          "id": 7,
          "question": "How could you get today’s day (e.g. “Monday”) from the date object?",
          "answer": "You need to make an array with Sunday at 0 index and Saturday at 7 index. Then use getDay() and find the day using your array."
        },
      
        {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "What does a for ... in loop do and what does it look like?",
          "answer": "It iterates over the enumerable properties in an object like this: for (var prop in obj) {// optionally, find only properties of this object, not the objects from which it inherits if (obj.hasOwnProperty(prop) { // do something"
        },
      
        {
          "id": 9,
          "question": "How do you access the function you are in (e.g. for a factorial)?",
          "answer": "Use the name of the function. Arguments.caller is deprecated."
        },
      
        {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "var s = String; typeof s will be what?",
          "answer": "'function'"
        }
      ]
    }  
  ],
  "meta": {
    "currentPage": 1,
    "nextPage": null,
    "prevPage": 1, 
    "totalPages": 2, 
    "totalCount": 2
  }
}